<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>curbings on User Manual (wiki) - Capital Parking Lot Lines Painting (CPLS)</title>
    <link>/tags/curbings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in curbings on User Manual (wiki) - Capital Parking Lot Lines Painting (CPLS)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 13:36:08 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/curbings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SOP for painting curbing on parking lot</title>
      <link>/posts/how-to-paint-curbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 13:36:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/how-to-paint-curbs/</guid>
      <description>SOP Gather the necessary materials and equipment: Paint curbing machine or paint sprayer Paint suitable for curbing Curbing templates (if applicable) Measuring tape or ruler Stencils (if desired) Masking tape or painter&amp;rsquo;s tape Personal protective equipment (PPE) including gloves, goggles, and a mask Prepare the work area: Ensure the parking lot is clean and free from debris. Use masking tape or painter&amp;rsquo;s tape to mark the boundaries of the curbing area, if needed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to paint Costco half circles</title>
      <link>/posts/half-circles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 13:36:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/half-circles/</guid>
      <description>Painting the Stencil:&#xA;Position the spray gun to only paint the stencil Ensure the paint sprayed evenly on the surface. Operating the Machine:&#xA;Ensure the paint sprayed evenly on the surface. Cleanup:&#xA;Clean the paint gun and machine thoroughly according to the manufacturer&amp;rsquo;s instructions. Safety and Final Checks:&#xA;Ensure the painted area is cordoned off until the paint is completely dry. Verify the circle is evenly painted and meets the required specifications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOP How to paint circles</title>
      <link>/posts/how-to-paint-circle/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 13:36:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/how-to-paint-circle/</guid>
      <description>Painting the Circle:&#xA;Position the machine at the starting point of the circle’s circumference. Align the back of the machine (where the paint gun is located) with the chalk line. Ensure the machine is level and stable. Operating the Machine:&#xA;Start the machine and engage the paint gun. Begin moving the machine forward, following the chalk line carefully. Maintain a steady speed to ensure an even application of paint. Continuously check the alignment of the paint gun with the chalk line.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
