<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wiki - Parking lot line striping - All SOPs on User Manual (wiki) - Capital Parking Lot Lines Painting (CPLS)</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Wiki - Parking lot line striping - All SOPs on User Manual (wiki) - Capital Parking Lot Lines Painting (CPLS)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 13:36:08 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SOP What to Ask Before Going to a Site</title>
      <link>/posts/question_to_ask/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 13:36:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/question_to_ask/</guid>
      <description>Questions you should Ask Before Going to a Site:&#xA;When and what time do you want me to be there? Confirm the exact date and time to arrive on site. What would be my role? Understand the specific responsibilities and tasks assigned. Roles may include: Social Media Photographer/Videographer: Responsible for capturing as many photos and videos as possible. Line Painter: Responsible for painting parking lot lines. Stencil Painter: Responsible for painting any stencils required.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOP: On Job Site (3/3) - Painting and Cleanup</title>
      <link>/posts/painting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 13:36:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/painting/</guid>
      <description>Painting Phase:&#xA;Start Painting:&#xA;Begin the painting process, ensuring lines are straight and measurements are correct. Take photos to document the process and results. Stencil Application:&#xA;Apply chalkline for stencils. Paint number and arrow stencils, as well as blue squares and handicap stencils if needed. Paint other required stencils. Cleaning Phase:&#xA;Make Corrections and Touch-Ups:&#xA;Correct any errors and perform necessary touch-ups. Remove All Shingles:&#xA;Remove shingles from the site. Collect All Garbage:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOP: On Job Site (2/3) - Preparation for Painting</title>
      <link>/posts/preparation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 13:36:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/preparation/</guid>
      <description>Preparation for Painting:&#xA;Prepare Line Painting Equipment:&#xA;Set up all necessary line painting equipment. Ensure the equipment is in good working condition. Pass the Blower:&#xA;Use a blower to remove dust and debris from the site. Ensure the surface is clean and ready for painting. Prepare Shingle:&#xA;Set up shingles as required for the job. Ensure they are correctly positioned and secure. Open Paint Pale:&#xA;Open the paint containers carefully.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Apply Chalkline in Parking Lot</title>
      <link>/posts/how-to-apply-chalkline-in-parking-lot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 13:36:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/how-to-apply-chalkline-in-parking-lot/</guid>
      <description>Equipment Chalk Chalkline Checklist Gather materials&#xA;Chalk line Chalk Measuring tape Straight edge Prepare the surface&#xA;Clean and dry the surface Determine the line placement&#xA;Measure and mark the line placement lightly with chalk Load the chalk line&#xA;Open the chalk line and fill it with chalk powder Set the line&#xA;Place one end of the chalk line at one end of the line you want to mark and secure it Hold the other end of the line taut and perpendicular to the ground Snap the line</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOP on how does Spray tip work</title>
      <link>/posts/how-spray-tip-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 13:36:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/how-spray-tip-work/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOP for painting curbing on parking lot</title>
      <link>/posts/how-to-paint-curbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 13:36:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/how-to-paint-curbs/</guid>
      <description>SOP Gather the necessary materials and equipment: Paint curbing machine or paint sprayer Paint suitable for curbing Curbing templates (if applicable) Measuring tape or ruler Stencils (if desired) Masking tape or painter&amp;rsquo;s tape Personal protective equipment (PPE) including gloves, goggles, and a mask Prepare the work area: Ensure the parking lot is clean and free from debris. Use masking tape or painter&amp;rsquo;s tape to mark the boundaries of the curbing area, if needed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleaning/Changing Gun Filter</title>
      <link>/posts/gun-filter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 13:36:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/gun-filter/</guid>
      <description>SOP: Cleaning/Changing Gun Filter Objectivebjective: To perform preventive maintenance and troubleshoot issues related to a thinning spray pattern or clogging in the Titan 3500 parking lot striping machine&amp;rsquo;s RX80 spray gun.&#xA;Tools and Materials Required:&#xA;Titan 3500 parking lot striping machine RX80 spray gun Lacquer thinner or cleaning solvent Cleaning brush or soft cloth Procedure:&#xA;Identify the Issue: If To perform preventive maintenance and troubleshoot issues reexperiencing a thinning spray pattern or consistent line width issues, suspect a potential clog or dirty filter in the RX80 spray gun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOP for how to create black box</title>
      <link>/posts/black-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 13:36:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/black-box/</guid>
      <description>Images SOP Gather the necessary materials and equipment: 3/8&amp;quot; plywood or 1/4&amp;quot; louan sheets Aerosol traffic black paint Plywood or similar material for creating frames Chalk or temporary marking tool Personal protective equipment (PPE) including gloves, goggles, and a mask Prepare the work area: Ensure you have a well-ventilated space or work outdoors. Set up a work table or area with sufficient space to accommodate the size and quantity of black boxes you need to create.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOP for visiting a site.</title>
      <link>/posts/visiting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 13:36:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/visiting/</guid>
      <description>SOP for visiting a site. Initial Contact: Upon receiving a request for a quote or inquiry from a potential client, acknowledge the request and express interest in visiting the site to assess the scope of the project. Schedule a Site Visit: Coordinate with the client to schedule a convenient time for the site visit. Consider factors such as the client&amp;rsquo;s availability and any specific requirements related to accessing the site. Prepare for the Site Visit: Familiarize yourself with the location and any available information about the project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to paint Costco half circles</title>
      <link>/posts/half-circles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 13:36:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/half-circles/</guid>
      <description>Painting the Stencil:&#xA;Position the spray gun to only paint the stencil Ensure the paint sprayed evenly on the surface. Operating the Machine:&#xA;Ensure the paint sprayed evenly on the surface. Cleanup:&#xA;Clean the paint gun and machine thoroughly according to the manufacturer&amp;rsquo;s instructions. Safety and Final Checks:&#xA;Ensure the painted area is cordoned off until the paint is completely dry. Verify the circle is evenly painted and meets the required specifications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOP How to paint circles</title>
      <link>/posts/how-to-paint-circle/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 13:36:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/how-to-paint-circle/</guid>
      <description>Painting the Circle:&#xA;Position the machine at the starting point of the circle’s circumference. Align the back of the machine (where the paint gun is located) with the chalk line. Ensure the machine is level and stable. Operating the Machine:&#xA;Start the machine and engage the paint gun. Begin moving the machine forward, following the chalk line carefully. Maintain a steady speed to ensure an even application of paint. Continuously check the alignment of the paint gun with the chalk line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOP for painting stencils, including numbers, letters, or symbols</title>
      <link>/posts/stencil/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 13:36:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/stencil/</guid>
      <description>SOP Gather the necessary materials and equipment: Stencils with the desired numbers, letters, or symbols Paint suitable for outdoor use and pavement surfaces Paint roller or paint sprayer Masking tape or painter&amp;rsquo;s tape Measuring tape or ruler Chalk or temporary marking paint Personal protective equipment (PPE) including gloves, goggles, and a mask Prepare the work area: Ensure the parking lot is clean and free from debris. Use masking tape or painter&amp;rsquo;s tape to mark the boundaries of the stencil area, if needed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOP for Posting Parking Lot Line Projects on Social Media</title>
      <link>/posts/social-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 13:36:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/social-media/</guid>
      <description>SOP for Posting Parking Lot Line Projects on Social Media Objective: The objective of this SOP is to provide guidelines for taking and posting pictures of parking lot line projects on social media platforms to showcase our work, promote our services, and maintain a positive online presence while respecting client confidentiality and adhering to legal and ethical considerations.&#xA;Procedure: Prioritizing Client Confidentiality: Obtain client consent: Before taking any pictures, seek explicit consent from the client to photograph and share images of the parking lot line project on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to shake WATER-based pale of paint</title>
      <link>/posts/how-to-shake-water-based-pale-of-paint/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 13:36:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/how-to-shake-water-based-pale-of-paint/</guid>
      <description>How to shake WATER-based pale of paint Introduction:&#xA;This guide will demonstrate the correct method for stirring paint to avoid issues such as air bubbles and uneven color distribution. Step-by-Step Instructions:&#xA;Preparation: Ensure you have all necessary equipment: paint can, stirrer, protective gloves, and a suitable surface to work on. Opening the Paint Can: Carefully open the lid of the paint can. If the can has been previously opened, watch for dry flakes that might fall into the fresh paint.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
