<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>job site preparation on User Manual (wiki) - Capital Parking Lot Lines Painting (CPLS)</title>
    <link>/tags/job-site-preparation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in job site preparation on User Manual (wiki) - Capital Parking Lot Lines Painting (CPLS)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 13:36:08 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/job-site-preparation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SOP What to Ask Before Going to a Site</title>
      <link>/posts/question_to_ask/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 13:36:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/question_to_ask/</guid>
      <description>Questions you should Ask Before Going to a Site:&#xA;When and what time do you want me to be there? Confirm the exact date and time to arrive on site. What would be my role? Understand the specific responsibilities and tasks assigned. Roles may include: Social Media Photographer/Videographer: Responsible for capturing as many photos and videos as possible. Line Painter: Responsible for painting parking lot lines. Stencil Painter: Responsible for painting any stencils required.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOP: On Job Site (2/3) - Preparation for Painting</title>
      <link>/posts/preparation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 13:36:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/preparation/</guid>
      <description>Preparation for Painting:&#xA;Prepare Line Painting Equipment:&#xA;Set up all necessary line painting equipment. Ensure the equipment is in good working condition. Pass the Blower:&#xA;Use a blower to remove dust and debris from the site. Ensure the surface is clean and ready for painting. Prepare Shingle:&#xA;Set up shingles as required for the job. Ensure they are correctly positioned and secure. Open Paint Pale:&#xA;Open the paint containers carefully.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
